Hi, and welcome back to Living in
Central Texas. This modern mansion on
the lake in Belton, Texas, is priced at
$1.7
million. It features just under 5,000
square ft of living space, high-end
finishes, a pool, and the most
breathtaking views. If you've been with
me for a minute, you know that I love
showcasing spectacular luxury homes, and
today's tour is no exception. If you
love luxury homes just as much as I do,
don't forget to like this video,
subscribe to my channel, and click the
bell icon so that you can stay uptodate
on luxury home tours and all things real
estate here in central Texas. This is a
4 bed, five bath home with a study built
in 2022 on
2.35 acres. It is actually
4,791 square ft, just under that 5,000
square foot mark. It is huge and it is
very
functional. As you can see from the
exterior, the front of this home is just
so striking with um very contemporary
feel, white stucco exterior, and really
well done landscaping.
This is a twostory home with a super
open floor plan, high ceilings, and
customsized windows. Actually, no matter
what room you're in, you can just really
see how bright and beautiful everything
is with the amount of windows that they
put in this home. To me, the windows in
this home really, really make this home.
um they let in so much light and
practically every room you can view the
lake. So they did a really really
fantastic job with that and it just
really adds to the overall elegance of
this home. The main floor has the
primary bedroom with an expansive
walk-in closet.
The onsuite bathroom is very luxurious
with a modern vanity, double sinks, a
walk-in shower, and large standalone
soaking
tub. The office is downstairs, but the
three additional bedrooms are all
located on the upper floor, each with
large windows, walk-in closets, and
magnificent views of Stillhouse Hollow
Lake.
A gas fireplace sets the stage in the
living room again with so much of that
natural light um really spanning the
deck across the entire backside of the
home. Take a look at this gorgeous
kitchen with stainless steel high-end
appliances, quartz countertops, and a
view to die for.
[Music]
There's also a 700 plus square ft game
room above the garage equipped with a
state-of-the-art golf game simulator
with direct access to a half bathroom as
well. As you can see, I am not a golfer,
but I gave it a good
[Music]
swing. Outside, you'll find a backyard
oasis with an outdoor kitchen, a private
cabana overlooking a perfect gunnite
pool, um, all overlooking that beautiful
view of Stillhouse Hollow Lake.
This is one of my favorite luxury homes.
I can't wait to hear what you think. I
mean, just check out this view. If you
would like more information on this home
or any other homes in the area, you can
find all my contact information below.
And if you would just like more
information on relocating to the area,
you can download my free relocation
guide. Till next time.
[Music]